{
    "subject": "resource/Sergio_Osme\u00f1a",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "Filipino lawyer and politician; 4th President of the Philippines",
    "human_readable": "Sergio Osme\u00f1a is described as a Filipino lawyer and politician, also known as the 4th President of the Philippines.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8834933638572693,
            "question": "What number president of the Philippines was Sergio Osme\u00f1a?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8393036127090454,
            "question": "What is Sergio Osme\u00f1a known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7942862510681152,
            "question": "What political role did Sergio Osme\u00f1a hold in the Philippines?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6713523268699646,
            "question": "What is Sergio Osme\u00f1a's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6184492111206055,
            "question": "What is Sergio Osme\u00f1a's legacy in Philippine history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5803943872451782,
            "question": "Can you name some key achievements of Sergio Osme\u00f1a during his presidency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5662254691123962,
            "question": "What were the major political events happening during Sergio Osme\u00f1a's presidency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5022911429405212,
            "question": "Besides being a politician, what other field did Sergio Osme\u00f1a work in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4936051368713379,
            "question": "How did Sergio Osme\u00f1a's background influence his political career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38698533177375793,
            "question": "Where was Sergio Osme\u00f1a born and raised?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sergio Osme\u00f1a is described as a Filipino lawyer and politician, also known as the 4th President of the Philippines.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2029_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Sergio Osme\u00f1a's background influence his political career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2029_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides being a politician, what other field did Sergio Osme\u00f1a work in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2029_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the major political events happening during Sergio Osme\u00f1a's presidency?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2029_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2029_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents describe Sergio Osme\u00f1a as a Filipino politician who served as the fourth President of the Philippines. Therefore, the information supports the given statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}